{
  "status": "success",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Time and Tide _____ for no man.",
      "answer": "waits",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["waits", "wait", "is waiting", "have waited"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Slow and steady _____ the race.",
      "answer": "wins",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["wins", "decides", "ends", "follow"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A friend in need is a friend",
      "answer": "indeed",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["indeed", "in fact", "in action", "in truth"]
    },
    {
      "question": "_____ stitch in time saves nine.",
      "answer": "a",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["a", "the", "a few", "the few"]
    },
    {
      "question": "An idle brain is the devils ______",
      "answer": "work shop",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["work shop", "work room", "work place", "work house"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Caesar’s wife must be above ______",
      "answer": "suspicion",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["suspicion", "average", "doubtful", "the law"]
    },
    {
      "question": "As you sow, _____ you reap.",
      "answer": "so",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["so", "as", "the", "or"]
    },
    {
      "question": "a blind man ́s wife _____ no colour.",
      "answer": "need",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["need", "necessary", "advantage", "used"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A dead _____ has no fear of wolves.",
      "answer": "donkey",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["donkey", "monkey", "vow", "tiger"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A fool at _____is a fool forever.",
      "answer": "forty",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["forty", "fifty", "sixty", "seventy"]
    }
  ]
}
